<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kristen Tidmuss</title>
    <link>https://KristenTidmuss.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kristen Tidmuss</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://KristenTidmuss.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>EvE Connection Finder</title>
      <link>https://KristenTidmuss.dev/projects/eveconnectionfinder/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KristenTidmuss.dev/projects/eveconnectionfinder/</guid>
      <description>This is a small project I created along side my friend Clayton. I came up with the idea when more and more frequently I would login to the game EvE Online after long breaks and have people recognise me and I would have no idea who they were.
To solve this issue I have created EvE Connection Finder, Simply type your name into the top box and either paste an individual or the entirety of the system into the second and hit submit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://KristenTidmuss.dev/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KristenTidmuss.dev/about/</guid>
      <description>Kris I am a 24 year old software developer currently living in Nottingham, UK. For the last 6 years I have been working for Quotient Sciences in Ruddington under many job roles. Most recently as an IT Application Support Analyst. Currently I am studying at Nottingham Trent University working towards a degree in software development along side my full time job.
Top 5 Skills    Soft Skills Hard Skills Programming Languages     Communication Software Development C#   Collaboration Database Development Python   Critical Thinking Web Development SQL   Problem Solving Git JS   Business Analysis Debugging HTML    Top 5 Hobbies  Developing small applications Tinkering with hardware Configuring linux servers Researching and experimenting with emerging technologies Watching movies and series with my SO  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
